americanbankingnews.com 2014-04-03

# Privacy Policy, Investment Disclaimer and Disclosures - American Banking News

**Investment Disclaimer**  

American Banking and Market News only information and content on this website is not meant to be a recommendation or an offer to buy or sell any security. American Banking and Market News staff members are not brokers, dealers or registered investment advisers and do not intend or attempt to influence the purchase or sale of any security. American Banking and Market News does not guarantee the accuracy or completeness of the content displayed in any section of this website.

Content from American Banking and Market News should not be used in any prospectus, offering memorandum or other disclosure attributable to any issuer of securities. No legal entity or individual is authorized to link to content on American Banking and Market News for the purpose of including any information into any disclosure to any investor or potential investor.

American Banking and Market News cannot be responsible for any loss that may be incurred by any person resulting for the use of this website or any material contained herein. The publishers of American Banking and Market News recommend that investors desiring to trade in securities do so cautiously and with the help of a personal financial advisor.

Links to other websites on American Banking and Market News should not be considered an endorsement of that website, their recommendations or products. Links to those sites are for informational purposes only. American Banking and Market News provides no responsibility for any loss caused by the material of any domain linked to in an American Banking and Market News article.

The Information and services contained in or made through this site may include or incorporate by reference “forward-looking statements” within the meaning of Section 27(a) of the Securities Act of 1933 and Section 21(e) of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934, including certain information with respect to plans and strategies of each featured company. For this purpose, any statements attributable to this site that are not statements of historical fact may be deemed to be forward-looking statements. Such statements are subject to various risks, uncertainties and assumptions about the featured companies, economic and market factors and the industries and assumptions about the featured companies do business, among other factors. Such statements are in no way guarantees of future performance or actual events. Results may differ materially from those expressed or forecasted by or concerning the featured companies due to a great many factors.

Never depend solely on the information contained in an Internet publication. The risk of fraudulent information exists with many Internet sites. [CLICK HERE](http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&source=web&cd=1&ved=0CBYQFjAA&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sec.gov%2Finvestor%2Fpubs%2Fcyberfraud.htm&ei=y8I4TYWcMcTTgQfnt9TfCA&usg=AFQjCNEf7uJivwKdXdCLqLksNn4JgYTX0w) to read the SEC Publication “Internet Fraud: How to Avoid Internet Investment Scams”

**Privacy Policy**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us using any of the methods listed on our contact page

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by this website and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, this website makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

This website does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

DoubleClick DART Cookie  
\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this website.  
\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this website and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include: Google AdSense, Tribal Fusion, AdBlade, NewsMax and Vibrant Media

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on this website send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

This website has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This website’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

### Advertising Disclosures

This website uses affiliate, contextual pay-per-click advertising and sponsored text links to generate advertising revenue to pay for operating costs such as hiring writers and maintaining the site’s technical infrastructure, which means this website may receive compensation or commissions when you click on an ad banner or hyperlink to an external website.

Affiliate and other advertising programs that American Banking and Market News currently participates in include Commission Junction, Google AdSense, Technorati Media, Lending Club, Prosper Marketplace, NetSeer and others. This website also receives compensation for links under the “Resources” column on the right-sidebar of the website. This website also participates in a number of affiliate programs through Commission Junction, including Audible.com, Mozy Backup, the Financial Times and HSBC Advance.

Text and image ads that appear in the right column, above articles and below articles on this website are third party Google AdSense, Technorati Media, ValueClick, Burst Media and direct buy ads. American Consumer News, LLC does not necessarily endorse products which are advertised on this website.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> .
